mp3dl.co.cc 2011-10-02

# Listen to Free Music Online - Disclaimer & Privacy Policy

MP3DL (mp3dl.co.cc) is a music search engine for locating music files over the Internet. We don't host and cached any music files, our crawler searches through the Net and indexes all the brand new and popular music files for your comfortable and fast search. We are glad to see you using our service. We hope it will be usefull to you and your friends, you'll enjoy our service and share your experience with your friends! Check back in from time to time to see what we've done new. If you have any questions or have something interesting to offer please feel free to contact us. 

  1. Mp3DL does not host and cached any of the music files displayed on this site.
  2. Mp3DL indexes these files which are located on youtube.com.
  3. All music files that are in this website solely for the purposes of education and information only.
  4. MP3DL not provide download link on MP3DL website and or embed media files for Third Party website to honor DMCA ISSUE or any copyrights protection laws.
  5. All the rights on the songs are the property of their respective owners.
  6. Required : [Adobe Flash Player](http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/) version 9 or latest and browser with javascript enable.
  7. **Social Contribution Networks**

List of website in the MP3DL index, and we call as "Social Contribution Networks" is, [youtube.com](http://youtube.com/).

(a). We do not have the right to set up, cencor and change the any music files that appear on this website, visitors and the holder the right to file objections is entitled to submit / reset the file so that we can not show (private access). Please visit the Term of Service, Copyright Policy or Privacy Policy of MP3DL's Social Contribution Networks.

(b). MP3DL just indexes any public music files from [youtube.com](http://youtube.com/).

(c). (MP3DL not responsible for the mistakes of others so or cause your music files listed in MP3DL.

(d). **Copyright / DMCA Policy** , If you are a copyright owner or an agent thereof and believe that some content infringes upon your copyrights, Please read all MP3DL disclaimer, mainly on poin of 7(a).

  1. If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at **media[-at-]mp3dl.co.cc**. 

At MP3DL, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by MP3DL and how it is used.

  2. **Log Files**
    1. Like many other Web sites, MP3DL makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.
    2. We use visitor search logs (words for search in the search box entry) to help and give idea for other visitors to found the page with a better result. without included any information on the poin 1. 
  3. **Cookies and Web Beacons**

MP3DLc does not use cookies.

  4. **DoubleClick DART Cookie**
    1. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on MP3DL.
    2. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to mp3dl.co.cc and other sites on the Internet.
    3. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, Amazon. 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on mp3dl.co.cc send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

MP3DL has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. MP3DL's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

media(-at-)mp3dl.co.cc
